export default [
    {
        question: "He is living in Paris",
        answer: "á",
        highlight: "in",
    },
    {
        question: "I bought this coat for $200",
        answer: "pour",
        highlight: "for",
    },
    {
        question: "It’s hard without money",
        answer: "sans",
        highlight: "without",
    },
    {
        question: "Mg Mg digs with a shovel.",
        answer: "avec",
        highlight: "with",
    },
    {
        question: "They go to school from 8:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m.",
        answer: "de",
        highlight: "from",
    },
    {
        question: "The bakery is close to the hotel.",
        answer: "á côté de",
        highlight: "close to",
    },
    {
        question: "I'm next to the swimming pool.",
        answer: "á côté de",
        highlight: "next to",
    },
    {
        question: "They are sitting behind",
        answer: "derrière",
        highlight: "behind",
    },
    {
        question: "They are sitting in front",
        answer: "devant",
        highlight: "in front",
    },
    {
        question: "Go on holidays with your couple or children and save up to 20 on your curise during all the season.",
        answer: "au long de",
        highlight: "during",
    },
    {
        question: "Declining buffalo herds and disease put many nations on the verge of extinction.",
        answer: "au bord de",
        highlight: "on the verge of",
    },
    {
        question: "Feel, relax, enjoy the best products at the center of Yangon.",
        answer: "au centre de",
        highlight: "at the center of",
    },
    {
        question: "This is going to happen in the middle of 2009",
        answer: "au milieu de",
        highlight: "in the middle of",
    },
    {
        question: "He lives at the top of this hill.",
        answer: "au sommet de",
        highlight: "at the top of",
    },
    {
        question: "Your shoes are at the bottom of your closet.",
        answer: "au fond de",
        highlight: "at the bottom of",
    },
    {
        question: "at the end of three days, the situation stabilized.",
        answer: "au bout de",
        highlight: "at the end of",
    },
    {
        question: "Prices available on request.",
        answer: "sur",
        highlight: "on",
    },
    {
        question: "Please check the question written above",
        answer: "dessus",
        highlight: "above",
    },
    {
        question: "Children are under parent’s protections.",
        answer: "sous",
        highlight: "under",
    },
    {
        question: "This price is listed below",
        answer: "dessous",
        highlight: "below",
    },
    {
        question: "We expect to finish the project in a year",
        answer: "dans",
        highlight: "in",
    },
    {
        question: "Nothing can be found inside the building",
        answer: "dedans",
        highlight: "inside",
    },
    {
        question: "The most populated city in France is Paris.",
        answer: "en",
        highlight: "in",
    },
    {
        question: "Myanmar gained independency in 1945",
        answer: "en",
        highlight: "in",
    },
    {
        question: "Here, take that and drop it by my house",
        answer: "chez moi",
        highlight: "my house",
    },
    {
        question: "Mitchell's out of his mind right now.",
        answer: "hors de",
        highlight: "out of",
    },
    {
        question: "Dr. Cranston's waiting outside for you.",
        answer: "dehors",
        highlight: "outside",
    },
    {
        question: " Jane parked her car on the side of the road.",
        answer: "au bord de",
        highlight: "on the side of",
    },
]